
let easyGames = {"0":{"question":"000000000000000000000030000205046780340897100807051000051703090072900350938012074","answer":"123475968769128543584639217215346789346897125897251436451763892672984351938512674"},"1":{"question":"800702930020050000070008020004006009000001206600247051401600890702004010005073060","answer":"846712935123459678579368124214536789357891246698247351431625897762984513985173462"},"2":{"question":"000020000234070509000006000123060800400089003090210456340097600070630940900000705","answer":"615924378234178569789356124123465897456789213897213456341597682578632941962841735"},"3":{"question":"054908000000005009709100005002007608465380107807610400501700000008020900900860072","answer":"254938716186275349739146285312457698465389127897612453521793864678524931943861572"},"4":{"question":"000000030000100400680300100000056000406789003897200506310675000070000001904831002","answer":"149527638723168495685394127231456879456789213897213546312675984578942361964831752"},"5":{"question":"804000032000000000009100008210300800006890010700210046030062900561980020980701500","answer":"854679132123458679679123458215346897346897215798215346437562981561984723982731564"},"6":{"question":"000007500200156089508230006103400807400700003000002005042601000705980021080020604","answer":"619847532234156789578239146123465897456798213897312465342671958765984321981523674"},"7":{"question":"000090000005208000009100040200007900000089000007612054321074590564923080008060402","answer":"412795863635248179789136245246357918153489627897612354321874596564923781978561432"},"8":{"question":"000000300003000780059000000004500000000000200708620513530842961040013805981000430","answer":"276189354413256789859437126324571698165398247798624513537842961642913875981765432"},"9":{"question":"000024007020078009678059024000405090000007200000210506300500902002901005905702600","answer":"139624857524178369678359124213465798456897213897213546341586972762931485985742631"},"10":{"question":"005010300103057000080030000000000098050000010000124536030002967568070003972043800","answer":"625819374143257689789436125214365798356798412897124536431582967568971243972643851"},"11":{"question":"002004000000009050680050100210465009405008010807120006021806090040000870000001623","answer":"152384967734619258689257134213465789465798312897123546321876495546932871978541623"},"12":{"question":"000000000100257089009030040012400006405389002000012000020000060743006521006021030","answer":"258964173134257689679138245312475896465389712897612354521743968743896521986521437"},"13":{"question":"007000003003006000400070120014500098360000270098064010032800967870600400000000030","answer":"627189543153426789489375126214537698365918274798264315532841967871693452946752831"},"14":{"question":"000000000200100007700056000003460089407090005598703006010000008040932671906008002","answer":"651247893234189567789356124123465789467891235598723416312674958845932671976518342"},"15":{"question":"000700000100349008780006200210405700000800360090037045500682007072900600064070020","answer":"345728916126349578789156234213465789457891362698237145531682497872914653964573821"},"16":{"question":"000000004140009678709046005302450860450698310600000050520003906000000001064020700","answer":"236785194145239678789146235312457869457698312698312457521873946873964521964521783"},"17":{"question":"000020000103060000000300000000000007300000004009001356531706942642900081097412560","answer":"458127639123869475976354128264593817315678294789241356531786942642935781897412563"},"18":{"question":"780000304123009000400070000204030780056097040000200506502901000641000050978000013","answer":"785126394123459678469378125214635789356897241897214536532941867641783952978562413"},"19":{"question":"700010043003408009050000000010350090005000012870000056531062980002080005900500021","answer":"798615243123478569456239178214356897365897412879124356531762984642981735987543621"},"20":{"question":"000001000004250700000009000000000008006008037809000415320080950640910872907605040","answer":"273841569194256783568379124712534698456198237839762415321487956645913872987625341"},"21":{"question":"005004093030100000000350100023075800400290017897000000041080906068901732000000480","answer":"715824693234169578689357124123475869456298317897613245341782956568941732972536481"},"22":{"question":"000000056120450009000370120200600890006090005780210003400002078000703040800041030","answer":"934128756127456389568379124251634897346897215789215463413562978692783541875941632"},"23":{"question":"802007005030009670070008200010075060456890320700000000000704006647000500080036042","answer":"862147935134259678579368214213475869456891327798623451325784196647912583981536742"},"24":{"question":"000000006005000400000057120120540708546000201790200504301620000800971005974030600","answer":"417382956235169487689457123123546798546798231798213564351624879862971345974835612"},"25":{"question":"090840037023560089000100056004306098007298014080070005700000902062000003000000000","answer":"596842137123567489478139256214356798357298614689471325731685942862914573945723861"},"26":{"question":"000049650000050700500200030000005890450090003706000405600014078040030000905600341","answer":"137849652264153789589276134312465897458791263796328415623514978841937526975682341"},"27":{"question":"200107006034060079070000023310540700460000030090000461000010980740080602080720310","answer":"259137846134268579678459123312546798467891235895372461523614987741983652986725314"},"28":{"question":"080000006000000000000000000010065007050710360096823015031040978840930600972081543","answer":"187394256324156789569278134213465897458719362796823415631542978845937621972681543"},"29":{"question":"000020000004000579000000128100050000000700200000293410040675002092830050875910630","answer":"587129346214368579936547128123456897459781263768293415341675982692834751875912634"},"30":{"question":"670384005000060000400120000204035000060090204007000006530070000740912803080400671","answer":"679384125123567489458129367214635798365798214897241536531876942746912853982453671"},"31":{"question":"080300012100008409006029070200506000365897024097000030030060000600950780900000205","answer":"789345612123678459456129378214536897365897124897214536538762941642951783971483265"},"32":{"question":"000000005024309600070000034210005809407896002008123050001500900060004000905000700","answer":"136478295524319678879652134213745869457896312698123457341587926762934581985261743"},"33":{"question":"010340007030157000500000030123005806056000072800020015000010960001004000982506041","answer":"218349657634157289579268134123475896456891372897623415345712968761984523982536741"},"34":{"question":"007143060003007089000200037214000098065000000798010350009600071641070000000031600","answer":"987143562123567489456289137214356798365798214798412356539624871641875923872931645"},"35":{"question":"000570000000100060009006000000450609400398200897012304000060928068021000002800516","answer":"613574892245189763789236145321457689456398271897612354134765928568921437972843516"},"36":{"question":"008090000030008079670100200010400890056000132090002400001873000064901380083504000","answer":"248697513135248679679135248312456897456789132897312456521873964764921385983564721"},"37":{"question":"060000015100400700050070200000060800000891020089720103530040078002080000006017302","answer":"768239415123456789954178236217365894345891627689724153531642978472983561896517342"},"38":{"question":"000000120020000079070100006000600897006800210089201003501700942600000085097400031","answer":"364597128125368479978124356213645897756839214489271563531786942642913785897452631"},"39":{"question":"070300420003408079000207000210030890000000000000004350000672084708940010902080760","answer":"175369428623418579489257136214536897357891642896724351531672984768943215942185763"},"40":{"question":"050300000003057600080020305204039700005001090897004000500840970040003051078615002","answer":"456398127123457689789126345214539768365781294897264513531842976642973851978615432"},"41":{"question":"401000000030040009000000024023405090540009230098207005010084050800070300974500680","answer":"451792863236148579789356124123465798547819236698237415312684957865971342974523681"},"42":{"question":"802701000000000089000300000000005807400879013708023064020510070501080000980632400","answer":"852791346134256789679348125213465897465879213798123564326514978541987632987632451"},"43":{"question":"780000400000400000000008000214635709305897200800142005031080907070000030000003050","answer":"782351496153469872649278513214635789365897241897142365431586927576924138928713654"},"44":{"question":"037200000000000000680157204003460007500710302706820040300074000870030600960500003","answer":"137246589425398716689157234213465897548719362796823145351674928874932651962581473"},"45":{"question":"000200160023000079408070200004000890059007600780002004000704000001620943040801006","answer":"597243168123568479468179235214356897359487612786912354632794581871625943945831726"},"46":{"question":"000000000105308600070000000003060790400091063869723400300002900002000347086034020","answer":"934617852125348679678259134213465798457891263869723415341572986592186347786934521"},"47":{"question":"002800000000126080000307000000400897050080200897000460034070000560040302000032641","answer":"712894536345126789689357124123465897456789213897213465234671958561948372978532641"},"48":{"question":"000000002000000000509030147214050780056007214807024035000500976070001050000703421","answer":"143675892728419563569238147214356789356897214897124635431582976672941358985763421"},"49":{"question":"080004502023568400007020008000356897000000100708041030030002000070900043942600000","answer":"689734512123568479457129368214356897365897124798241635531472986876915243942683751"},"50":{"question":"000007821000300000000120000200050008450090006000270154031700962000012080980005410","answer":"349567821125348679678129345213456798457891236896273154531784962764912583982635417"},"51":{"question":"000000170020400509600000230000005000000007410890214356530000981740980020906500000","answer":"459362178123478569678159234214635897365897412897214356532746981741983625986521743"},"52":{"question":"500000000000000600680200157000400890056098070008002305010706928840921003060080010","answer":"521867439734159682689234157273415896456398271198672345315746928847921563962583714"},"53":{"question":"080100500000060000400009000010000700065008214798214360030020900640970050809001030","answer":"983142576152367489476589123214635798365798214798214365537826941641973852829451637"},"54":{"question":"900600300000008000000000000014000007370091000689000503001900782742183060096572400","answer":"927614358163758249458239176214365897375891624689427513531946782742183965896572431"},"55":{"question":"090500000100000579007009068200056090300000420005900316030600080806093052002840030","answer":"698517243123468579457239168214356897369781425785924316531672984846193752972845631"},"56":{"question":"070003000120450089468100030210300807057000020680000153501640000040900500000500042","answer":"975283416123456789468179235214365897357891624689724153531642978742938561896517342"},"57":{"question":"000000056023007000000089100204000090365090004000104503031806902040013800900452631","answer":"789241356123567489456389127214635798365798214897124563531876942642913875978452631"},"58":{"question":"000034020100507009000029057210006090375200610000001035000002001000905863891040500","answer":"759834126132567489648129357214356798375298614986471235563782941427915863891643572"},"59":{"question":"900020000004000079007000000000050090059000306000003005040075000692831750075294631","answer":"913427568584316279267589143436152897159748326728963415341675982692831754875294631"},"60":{"question":"080007256000346009070008030003405000406789300798023060500600900800090003000034021","answer":"384917256125346789679258134213465897456789312798123465531672948842591673967834521"},"61":{"question":"002000000045029670000007120003006700006000001000001406031864590508902300970015862","answer":"712638945345129678689457123123546789496783251857291436231864597568972314974315862"},"62":{"question":"030620000000008000000100237200007896406801070890000105300000081682003704901000020","answer":"739625418124378569568149237213457896456891372897236145345762981682913754971584623"},"63":{"question":"205000640004000009600050023300046007406090200780032056003671080060020310040380002","answer":"275913648134268579698754123312546897456897231789132456523671984867429315941385762"},"64":{"question":"000900000000040679089256034003000807050089013007120056030070002600000345008030760","answer":"364917528125348679789256134213465897456789213897123456531674982672891345948532761"},"65":{"question":"290140007030057009008009020310475000400001073080900415000530900800700000005006732","answer":"296148357134257689578369124312475896459681273687923415721534968863792541945816732"},"66":{"question":"060038000000069500500040006003056700007800000698070000301684007005013600040720010","answer":"162538479734169582589247136213456798457892361698371245321684957875913624946725813"},"67":{"question":"060780510000000089780100006000007090406008120800002300500864003030900850070003461","answer":"263789514145236789789145236312457698456398127897612345521864973634971852978523461"},"68":{"question":"000000004030150000009000135103460009057801000098700000041600090860007342972500816","answer":"516378924234159678789246135123465789457891263698723451341682597865917342972534816"},"69":{"question":"000015002020000060000040130013056080000008213090020540531800974800004000904530000","answer":"347615892125389467689247135213456789456798213798123546531862974862974351974531628"},"70":{"question":"000000000005000000078140005200006097400807000080310006027080054001924703800030621","answer":"132568479645279138978143265213456897456897312789312546327681954561924783894735621"},"71":{"question":"700042000023000008060008230210635709300000600806420053502900860640000092900050000","answer":"758342916123569478469178235214635789375891624896427153532914867641783592987256341"},"72":{"question":"000008000230007089570009024023070000406090000780623010300780900040930050907010308","answer":"691248537234157689578369124123475896456891273789623415315784962842936751967512348"},"73":{"question":"045190000000057680009000000010000098000800006096004051008000902001002873970683504","answer":"645198237123457689789236145214365798357819426896724351438571962561942873972683514"},"74":{"question":"300905102100060009000000000210056708050000010000713204730604800842501060065000400","answer":"376945182124368579589127346213456798457289613698713254731694825842531967965872431"},"75":{"question":"000000038000008009060379020000005007000890213789000450001704905005016000043082060","answer":"297451638134268579568379124312645897456897213789123456621734985875916342943582761"},"76":{"question":"070160300020000079060300000000604800040090200700210030037006900601980742092740003","answer":"574169328123458679968372154215634897346897215789215436437526981651983742892741563"},"77":{"question":"300715000005300070070008000003056709000000203890003046501600007060900850004572361","answer":"348715692125369478679248135213456789456897213897123546531684927762931854984572361"},"78":{"question":"090000804204000509570000100000000098056890000709210460010604007800020340900700602","answer":"691375824234168579578942136123456798456897213789213465312684957867529341945731682"},"79":{"question":"460001090000060508000208100000350000050000004007004005031902807740603900082700063","answer":"468531792129467538573298146814356279256179384397824615631942857745683921982715463"},"80":{"question":"805070600100400080070208005004005090050091004068004300000080000500017023002603510","answer":"845179632123456789679238145214365897357891264968724351431582976586917423792643518"},"81":{"question":"000080002000006000480037006004065897367001020098720000630000008042070561975008000","answer":"716589342253146789489237156124365897367891425598724613631452978842973561975618234"},"82":{"question":"908123005100000789050080103004065000005090004080000000000042070642070500097531062","answer":"978123645123456789456789123214365897365897214789214356531642978642978531897531462"},"83":{"question":"000070194020009000000008030004030009000897000708000350000081940840923000061705820","answer":"385276194426319578179458236614532789253897461798164352532681947847923615961745823"},"84":{"question":"000035918020000500500107004200006709006000100098502306400001092050024000060873001","answer":"674235918123489567589167234215346789346798125798512346437651892851924673962873451"},"85":{"question":"000000200230108000070000008123400890000089310700312400000070980001003020060804501","answer":"814697253235148679679235148123456897456789312798312465342571986581963724967824531"},"86":{"question":"000000905000000008580007000103005800006092310790603450000580706807920503040730000","answer":"612348975374159628589267134123475869456892317798613452231584796867921543945736281"},"87":{"question":"000000000020300600080100045203008000507209010698013204351080000800970001002501008","answer":"436895127125347689789126345213458796547269813698713254351684972864972531972531468"},"88":{"question":"000009030100006089079230000004005800350800264900720300030082070586907003090603008","answer":"845179632123456789679238145214365897357891264968724351431582976586917423792643518"},"89":{"question":"040030060030000079609147005000450700406789123800302046300500000060070000070600054","answer":"742935861135268479689147235213456798456789123897312546321594687564873912978621354"},"90":{"question":"400000000000209070689347005003456700546090230000103000021075900000912000007634002","answer":"472581693135269478689347125213456789546798231798123546321875964864912357957634812"},"91":{"question":"084000005000050000000208000010300600346781590708000010001095820050100903967020051","answer":"284916735193457286675238149519342678346781592728569314431695827852174963967823451"},"92":{"question":"300700105000056700500009200210000800456897300089200006031000078040000020072008541","answer":"394782165128456739567139284213645897456897312789213456631524978845971623972368541"},"93":{"question":"800100070020000000067080020010004008000090015009205306400020907058071400002503801","answer":"893152674124367589567489123215634798346798215789215346431826957658971432972543861"},"94":{"question":"090030040100000080008100005004360890009780406706000100600500900840007312070803004","answer":"597238641123456789468179235214365897359781426786924153631542978845697312972813564"},"95":{"question":"340000000000000009009006205010457896460300127000600000000800963600920500938061700","answer":"341295678526738419789146235213457896465389127897612354152874963674923581938561742"},"96":{"question":"010009530300120079000307004123400807457800003000000415031000900004900000070506342","answer":"712649538345128679689357124123465897457891263896273415231784956564932781978516342"},"97":{"question":"000010000104207089079400023010546700000800036096700000600934000003000960085070001","answer":"268319457134257689579468123312546798457891236896723514621934875743185962985672341"},"98":{"question":"000000361000056080670108040000047008000890007700000134400005970800900006900710853","answer":"285479361134256789679138245521347698346891527798562134413685972857923416962714853"},"99":{"question":"030000000020000009670050100010400806046090310807106425000600000762910583000020760","answer":"431769258528341679679258134315472896246895317897136425153687942762914583984523761"},"100":{"question":"000005000000000078600007200210050709450801300000720050530608040708912500002500010","answer":"179285634325469178684137295216354789457891326893726451531678942748912563962543817"},"101":{"question":"610000090204060008000200006023056009000090002000300005301005900762930801085700040","answer":"618573294234169578579248136123456789456897312897312465341685927762934851985721643"},"102":{"question":"910507020205100670008009045000456000407090030000072051040620980000004010000903564","answer":"914567823235148679678239145123456798457891236869372451341625987596784312782913564"},"103":{"question":"700001000004008000000070130000065090456097200800100000340082060600000581985710042","answer":"729431856134658729568279134217365498456897213893124675341582967672943581985716342"},"104":{"question":"000200100003060000400030050214306897000000610608712340730005004800970063060803001","answer":"576284139123569478489137256214356897357498612698712345731625984842971563965843721"},"105":{"question":"400000008000489060000207000014530780065008240790004056040670803006905000900003010","answer":"452361978173489562689257134214536789365798241798124356541672893836915427927843615"},"106":{"question":"900000000200008679007249130020060090450001006670080405315874000700000000800000741","answer":"981637254234158679567249138123465897458791326679382415315874962742916583896523741"},"107":{"question":"409000632005106000000000100020450806000398210807002304050800970700000063061500020","answer":"419785632235146789678239145123457896546398217897612354352864971784921563961573428"},"108":{"question":"070000000200058600680207000020405800000000017098613050000704962007920543002030081","answer":"175369428234158679689247135321475896456892317798613254513784962867921543942536781"},"109":{"question":"500040003200050000600030005123060780008791006000080400005800900800904502972513060","answer":"517248693234659178689137245123465789458791326796382451345826917861974532972513864"},"110":{"question":"000000000230000000009030040100470006065300071798600403340091700017026004080000502","answer":"851964237234157689679238145123479856465382971798615423342591768517826394986743512"},"111":{"question":"000020060000008000060009208000306807008090610009400000530002046706013080890645001","answer":"985724163123568479467139258214356897358297614679481325531872946746913582892645731"},"112":{"question":"005080000120000000709000200204000098350098024097204036031000802502841070008000000","answer":"645382917123479685789156243214635798356798124897214536431967852562841379978523461"},"113":{"question":"000000300030260500567340100210056800400001063070020400021670080045080601800104000","answer":"982517346134268579567349128213456897458791263679823415321675984745982631896134752"},"114":{"question":"002070000000200009008000123213506090006897031700000540501762084820010005060000710","answer":"392671458145238679678459123213546897456897231789123546531762984827914365964385712"},"115":{"question":"050000000130267089600000000000070090065080702798610305300090000507006901900021050","answer":"852139476134267589679458123213574698465983712798612345381795264527846931946321857"},"116":{"question":"000000000003050009000009300215006098346700000809210030031600970602070013900030004","answer":"794823561163457289528169347215346798346798152879215436431682975652974813987531624"},"117":{"question":"064105000003007000070200100205046090346080210008500460400000000032071850057004630","answer":"864195327123467589579238146215346798346789215798512463481653972632971854957824631"},"118":{"question":"062000050100200600000460000000040708400000030000000514301604970740002861806100042","answer":"962318457134257689578469123213546798457891236689723514321684975745932861896175342"},"119":{"question":"294010070030000009078049120300050708006098200009003000000030860840001050967580300","answer":"294815673135267489678349125312456798456798231789123546521934867843671952967582314"},"120":{"question":"000000060120670400400000170010000890065000010807042036540700980030020701001480020","answer":"759214368123678459486359172214536897365897214897142536542761983638925741971483625"},"121":{"question":"090020000005060480600040235200000008056098300089210540500682004042000003907034000","answer":"394825167125367489678149235213456798456798312789213546531682974842971653967534821"},"122":{"question":"000000000006070000700040006003456700065090300897120560000964800600031925970002643","answer":"238615497546279138719348256123456789465897312897123564352964871684731925971582643"},"123":{"question":"000500070003060080407080006214350790065000410790000305039000040000870900800903600","answer":"186534279923167584457289136214356798365798412798412365539621847641875923872943651"},"124":{"question":"004000900000300600009000034203000860406000320000603005001582006078906000062704081","answer":"634178952125349678789265134213457869456891327897623415341582796578916243962734581"},"125":{"question":"009603000000000460060000308210007090075096010090010573006000042041930080080400031","answer":"429683157853721469167549328214357896375896214698214573536178942741932685982465731"},"126":{"question":"000873105000040070000000200013460089400000312007310400001080067564030820000621003","answer":"642873195135249678789156234213465789456798312897312456321584967564937821978621543"},"127":{"question":"740000905100009000500067034000070060057600000098200300002580090871900523905703480","answer":"746832915123459678589167234214375869357698142698214357432581796871946523965723481"},"128":{"question":"200040037034250609008360100000070006007008003009000400700504000843010002900082341","answer":"296841537134257689578369124312475896457698213689123475721534968843916752965782341"},"129":{"question":"000000020003000009070230006014356000056007004089020005001682000002973501800415032","answer":"145769823623548179978231456214356798356897214789124365531682947462973581897415632"},"130":{"question":"070000060000460080068009040015040008000298005089071004400002006756910032890650001","answer":"974825163123467589568139247215346798347298615689571324431782956756914832892653471"},"131":{"question":"040109000003000000079200000204000006050091000097000000030700050765983421981542763","answer":"546139287123857649879264135214375896658491372397628514432716958765983421981542763"},"132":{"question":"300915000050278300000006005000407600400089203097000451500000980030500710004000532","answer":"342915867156278349789346125213457698465189273897623451521734986638592714974861532"},"133":{"question":"000000300034006000670208145103005800406700210800012504002500000000024031900603050","answer":"518947326234156789679238145123465897456789213897312564342591678765824931981673452"},"134":{"question":"000070600000000080000009005020465090406790200089310456340507908002080000007000502","answer":"215873649974256183638149725123465897456798231789312456341527968562981374897634512"},"135":{"question":"000980002100300000000207034013065000506708203700100400300000008070030621002814300","answer":"435981762127346589689257134213465897546798213798123456351672948874539621962814375"},"136":{"question":"040500000100060008079200046204356700000891004608024005401000050700100093905070021","answer":"846517932123469578579238146214356789357891264698724315431982657762145893985673421"},"137":{"question":"000000000000079000780046105013050080005090037897600450000064890670900000934500762","answer":"146285379352179648789346125213457986465891237897623451521764893678932514934518762"},"138":{"question":"400002000000008000080007234000005000060009000700010320531706982870590000940020751","answer":"413962578257438169689157234124375896365289417798614325531746982872591643946823751"},"139":{"question":"000000001025340000009000004003470869056801300098000100530000406847900502902500080","answer":"374268951125349678689157234213475869456891327798623145531782496847936512962514783"},"140":{"question":"740000030020000500000200000200056780357098204008700000402005007860902450900043601","answer":"746581932123469578589237146214356789357198264698724315432615897861972453975843621"},"141":{"question":"390084507105000000670000120010470008006891200709620015500000900030900050000042831","answer":"392184567145267389678359124213475698456891273789623415521738946834916752967542831"},"142":{"question":"208000050004000009070060023000046708400890206800023004020034805040100002905002340","answer":"268319457134257689579468123312546798457891236896723514621934875743185962985672341"},"143":{"question":"576000002020069078000100006214605089007000060600200503030480020000910030000050041","answer":"576348192123569478489127356214635789357891264698274513731486925845912637962753841"},"144":{"question":"090800010034000089008049000000000896400300000800612340005784000007921400000000728","answer":"592837614734156289168249537213475896456398172879612345325784961687921453941563728"},"145":{"question":"000900000123400060789000100000037006050009407800004200008090041040010983901040602","answer":"465921378123478569789356124214537896356289417897164235538692741642715983971843652"},"146":{"question":"000000005105000060079408100013040009050800001090020046500780604800004007007605012","answer":"384261975125379468679458123213546789456897231798123546531782694862914357947635812"},"147":{"question":"387500000020378509009004370213000897000000123000000045600780050800900200900635000","answer":"387519462426378519159264378213456897564897123798123645631782954875941236942635781"},"148":{"question":"000000200000000080000240100000065798050700002007302406305000967082936001961004820","answer":"418693275239157684576248139123465798654789312897312456345821967782936541961574823"},"149":{"question":"070009060005346080689007040000000090406091030000200050531870000007002010900000873","answer":"374189562125346789689527341213458697456791238798263154531874926867932415942615873"},"150":{"question":"000000000204100780009348105120005890456070200798010056001027900060000000087001000","answer":"815792364234156789679348125123465897456879213798213456541627938362984571987531642"},"151":{"question":"407000068005000400009000230010400090046780312708200546000002904800500003000804000","answer":"427935168365128479189647235213456897546789312798213546651372984874591623932864751"},"152":{"question":"002085470300007000008009035000000008000091062009020004200008057080072640706530020","answer":"692385471351247986478619235123456798547891362869723514234968157985172643716534829"},"153":{"question":"090000000000300000500009030013080006406091300089603015000812900842007001970506000","answer":"394158672127364859568279134213485796456791328789623415635812947842937561971546283"},"154":{"question":"008000501000000008569008034003460700050897100090210056002081067600000010901000000","answer":"238649571714352698569178234123465789456897123897213456342581967675934812981726345"},"155":{"question":"000090000004000609780036040123005008000000300000302000300578001001900800978640523","answer":"516894237234157689789236145123465798465789312897312456342578961651923874978641523"},"156":{"question":"000100400100050080500079103000540000056308210709610304305004001090705840007021006","answer":"932186475174253689568479123213547968456398217789612354325864791691735842847921536"},"157":{"question":"000000000000100609789050034020060000056780200890012456300000060078600901061070325","answer":"614839572235147689789256134423965718156784293897312456342591867578623941961478325"},"158":{"question":"000000300100406789500000040204300807000090004098704503400602958065000470000000600","answer":"746189325123456789589237146214365897357891264698724513431672958865913472972548631"},"159":{"question":"900080070000000000078239106010006090305790204700002060591020000600001025000900031","answer":"956184372123567489478239156214356798365798214789412563591623847637841925842975631"},"160":{"question":"260000000100000460009000000300047000000100300097360014501034090648971005073605841","answer":"264713958135289467789456123312547689456198372897362514521834796648971235973625841"},"161":{"question":"602079000130040009000000000003005000400090000096720415320587960561030782908000000","answer":"642179358135248679789356124213465897457891236896723415324587961561934782978612543"},"162":{"question":"400000002103000080069230047210300098300009214000120630000000071005910020981602400","answer":"478591362123467589569238147214356798356789214897124635632845971745913826981672453"},"163":{"question":"700300020003000007000060100004035080000000004897124000531406892000912500970800041","answer":"715348926683291457249567138124635789356789214897124365531476892468912573972853641"},"164":{"question":"300040000000007300600058120000470890000890037890023451000080900700032518002000003","answer":"318249675245167389679358124123475896456891237897623451531784962764932518982516743"},"165":{"question":"000200000034000000007000003100540607050701208780060510340020070670000802092070301","answer":"518234769934687125267159483123548697456791238789362514341825976675913842892476351"},"166":{"question":"004000690006000000009000200010000780000800025590703106600000050840510963975630800","answer":"124375698386249571759168234213456789467891325598723146631982457842517963975634812"},"167":{"question":"040020000000000700000309020200030608000100047780064503400072956672040031095000070","answer":"948721365123456789567389124214537698356198247789264513431872956672945831895613472"},"168":{"question":"000003040004000009500000000312400090450098000709312406000830970001070003003004861","answer":"127983645634157289598246137312465798456798312789312456265831974841679523973524861"},"169":{"question":"018035600030060078000200000100056789046890000097300500000604900064900001900500364","answer":"418735692235169478679248135123456789546897213897312546351684927764923851982571364"},"170":{"question":"300005000140009060700036200210000000406300002000012450500070006604000510938500724","answer":"362745891145289367789136245213457689456398172897612453521874936674923518938561724"},"171":{"question":"000725306020000079060000200200300097000090024009010000430001080670902403092003701","answer":"918725346324168579567439218286354197153897624749216835435671982671982453892543761"},"172":{"question":"090000000100000000067000103010540790456008200089010450031850940002901365075630000","answer":"398125674124367589567489123213546798456798231789213456631852947842971365975634812"},"173":{"question":"000094060200108350000306100100405000057010206608700415000007000004902571072581000","answer":"315294768246178359789356124123465897457819236698723415531647982864932571972581643"},"174":{"question":"042001300000060409000348125003006790406009203008103060301000002004012607007000001","answer":"842591376135267489679348125213456798456789213798123564361874952584912637927635841"},"175":{"question":"007093400003400009409070000204000000308700046796824001630502008800900020900607010","answer":"187293465523468179469175832214356987358719246796824351631542798875931624942687513"},"176":{"question":"004000002000009308080030000003400000460090210800300405530807604008940521940001837","answer":"314586972256179348789234156123465789465798213897312465531827694678943521942651837"},"177":{"question":"700293060204068579600450000000000090005700030897010045002000000000020006906831752","answer":"751293468234168579689457123123546897465789231897312645312675984578924316946831752"},"178":{"question":"508000007000070008070008000203040700406897001000010040041000002002901804905720310","answer":"528139467364275198179468523213546789456897231897312645741683952632951874985724316"},"179":{"question":"000000400000006009500047100200460800450109000090723010341600905805000041000004370","answer":"726891453134256789589347162213465897457189236698723514341678925875932641962514378"},"180":{"question":"900003040100207680067080123000500008406090230000002400020870005005900802009020010","answer":"982163547134257689567489123213546798456798231798312456321874965645931872879625314"},"181":{"question":"000040060000260009000000004000050800057801200090023405600500903745032081083604050","answer":"279145368134268579568379124312456897457891236896723415621587943745932681983614752"},"182":{"question":"000000001005200079009006000012007908400309007007012304521793400048000703003860510","answer":"264975831135248679789136245312457968456389127897612354521793486648521793973864512"},"183":{"question":"800000000000000009009130245210305800006809004700204036430627058000081070007043610","answer":"845792361123456789679138245214365897356879124798214536431627958562981473987543612"},"184":{"question":"087000001020000000409120307004536080060807124708014530006000002001050000040700805","answer":"687345291123679458459128367214536789365897124798214536536481972871952643942763815"},"185":{"question":"000100000020060400068300000210600807006897014780040350001000042600003701890410003","answer":"475128639123569478968374125214635897356897214789241356531786942642953781897412563"},"186":{"question":"000004070023507000400209130210630098006090204090140356530000040009001803040070000","answer":"985314672123567489467289135214635798356798214798142356531826947679451823842973561"},"187":{"question":"900000000000000000070200040010006097307001002600700315400675901005103600801942750","answer":"923418576148567239576239148214356897357891462689724315432675981795183624861942753"},"188":{"question":"700061090003000060600000000010030080306798215800125300001000900562000470908040031","answer":"724861593153279864689354127215436789346798215897125346431687952562913478978542631"},"189":{"question":"030018000004000070609007105213000089007891200800000000301002096502080010070036542","answer":"735618924124359678689247135213465789457891263896723451341572896562984317978136542"},"190":{"question":"040000800000000009609307105123056098456080000897203006012000000570602900060000000","answer":"241569837735418269689327145123756498456981372897243516912874653574632981368195724"},"191":{"question":"000080000124307689000240030213005008457801063600720004040000902000000046902030070","answer":"536189427124357689789246135213465798457891263698723514341678952875912346962534871"},"192":{"question":"805209000023006709000008020000500806350891074000620000501002000600980500087160402","answer":"865279143123456789479318625214537896356891274798624351531742968642983517987165432"},"193":{"question":"000203900100000008000000120014300009356800014098100300531040890062900000947002600","answer":"485213967123679548679458123214365789356897214798124356531746892862931475947582631"},"194":{"question":"000037528200140009678000000120465800407090000009002015010704000000010000790526080","answer":"941637528235148679678259134123465897457891263869372415312784956586913742794526381"},"195":{"question":"009010340100400080068379005200530600000092001095160030502000000000920810081703002","answer":"759218346123456789468379125214537698376892451895164237532681974647925813981743562"},"196":{"question":"000600000000078500000000007200300896356890002780000305630700054805903720072004000","answer":"197635248423178569568249137214357896356891472789426315631782954845963721972514683"},"197":{"question":"072000000104000600000109200200400007056000302789310065020080900690020703840936520","answer":"972643158134258679568179234213465897456897312789312465325781946691524783847936521"},"198":{"question":"000000000020460009500030140005046700000800625000700304031000057000953460006074830","answer":"164597283328461579597238146215346798743819625689725314431682957872953461956174832"},"199":{"question":"000094000145030080609100030203000890006879103090312000001000008000020000067581342","answer":"382694571145237689679158234213465897456879123798312456521743968834926715967581342"},"200":{"question":"000009008000100000089057123023046007050091230896273000002700060560002700970010040","answer":"741329658235168479689457123123546897457891236896273514312784965564932781978615342"},"201":{"question":"000100865020008409000009120210000700006097200709004350401000007600000540800041632","answer":"947132865123568479568479123214356798356897214789214356431625987672983541895741632"},"202":{"question":"000800000130000000009346005012400780406790030097103506021000807603082010040070050","answer":"265817493134259678789346125312465789456798231897123546521934867673582914948671352"},"203":{"question":"804021600000000080507009020000034800000007210089210006001502900650970431970100062","answer":"894721653123456789567389124215634897346897215789215346431562978652978431978143562"},"204":{"question":"500190300123400080009000000000000790350009064690704010401082006002903000975601032","answer":"546198327123457689789236145214365798357819264698724513431582976862973451975641832"},"205":{"question":"001030000234009060000056034020000000000098002090312006300680945006021800008043621","answer":"561834297234179568789256134123465789645798312897312456312687945456921873978543621"},"206":{"question":"030000570040207080009100034300405708007090020006072045520000060060903800903506010","answer":"238649571145237689679158234312465798457891326896372145521784963764913852983526417"},"207":{"question":"009184062100000000400209157010300000300400000806010004580001000037020840041803020","answer":"759184362123567489468239157214356798375498216896712534582641973637925841941873625"},"208":{"question":"070000841030260509500007200003056008056700123790012000020000900847900650000800307","answer":"672593841134268579589147236213456798456789123798312465321675984847931652965824317"},"209":{"question":"049000000100000000078009200002400790000090060806002014020003040000920851904705623","answer":"249537186135268479678149235312456798457891362896372514521683947763924851984715623"},"210":{"question":"400007000020000579508120300004350090057891460009200000000002900865040720000010083","answer":"493567218126438579578129346214356897357891462689274135731682954865943721942715683"},"211":{"question":"047100000000409008000000000000506000356700240098010065430025897862900050070800610","answer":"547182936123469578689357124214536789356798241798214365431625897862971453975843612"},"212":{"question":"000780360234156009670009105000465097006090000007000406300001908062008530900000004","answer":"519784362234156789678239145123465897456897213897312456345621978762948531981573624"},"213":{"question":"000100060000200079089057104210405008000000200000023010021700050500032781008016342","answer":"472189563135264879689357124213475698847691235956823417321748956564932781798516342"},"214":{"question":"060020950205000400000000100003040609040208071090360000002600094050914030074002500","answer":"167423958235189467489756123723541689546298371891367245312675894658914732974832516"},"215":{"question":"560004000100060000070100356200000000356090100800041503601050947702016030000403000","answer":"563784291129365478478129356214538769356297184897641523631852947742916835985473612"},"216":{"question":"040030006000108409000000100123506708450807001709003060002604080500081042890005010","answer":"941732856235168479678459123123546798456897231789213564312674985567981342894325617"},"217":{"question":"405000000030000000000030000000458000047300208698712453050004070060500934074683500","answer":"415267389739845162286139745123458697547396218698712453351924876862571934974683521"},"218":{"question":"000800075000240000678050000010070006000008700080012003020080960007901040800736521","answer":"249863175135247689678159234912374856453698712786512493321485967567921348894736521"},"219":{"question":"000000000000036700679000034200005090050780123798302406001670040004591072000004305","answer":"382947561145236789679158234213465897456789123798312456521673948834591672967824315"},"220":{"question":"004000001150009347000130006310006080465000003800002005021003004040000518070540632","answer":"234675891156289347789134256312456789465798123897312465521863974643927518978541632"},"221":{"question":"781040630000000000500300024003065800050800063608023051000500906000030510075012308","answer":"781249635234156789569378124123465897457891263698723451312584976846937512975612348"},"222":{"question":"000000000000000000060008123014000080006097200090024306630950807870203061900086002","answer":"123569478487312695569478123214635789356897214798124356632951847875243961941786532"},"223":{"question":"700020000104000000589107000000006708457000060608000154340080020072000610000012480","answer":"736529841124368579589147236213456798457891362698273154341685927872934615965712483"},"224":{"question":"000520040030000000000000020023406700457001000009200405302085904740902051905004032","answer":"671528349234169587598347126123456798457891263869273415312685974746932851985714632"},"225":{"question":"000300010100000000400100235000030000057802100009710052030085964862000573900603021","answer":"576328419123459687498167235214536798357892146689714352731285964862941573945673821"},"226":{"question":"000000000020300000679058103203506000460801235005003400530080900000035800986004050","answer":"354127689128369547679458123213546798467891235895273416531682974742935861986714352"},"227":{"question":"019720346230000000067049020100000897400800003708200065040000002601930000902080030","answer":"819725346234168579567349128123456897456897213798213465345671982681932754972584631"},"228":{"question":"207000008100000400080140005002456700450700103700302040020870004874001000963500001","answer":"247635918135289467689147235312456789456798123798312546521873694874961352963524871"},"229":{"question":"006000103100400009008009006000300790000000000689014025001003057705640832802005604","answer":"926587143173462589548139276214356798357298461689714325461823957795641832832975614"},"230":{"question":"040897031035200000080100200302400097007000020000000300021000970873000000964570012","answer":"246897531135246789789135246312458697457369128698712354521684973873921465964573812"},"231":{"question":"000000200120500489450200100200030000308000004579008360600820007002050041905106000","answer":"896341275123567489457289136214635798368792514579418362631824957782953641945176823"},"232":{"question":"010097320000000579709230000000000007507009061600000405301900002860000014074020053","answer":"415697328236148579789235146123456897547389261698712435351964782862573914974821653"},"233":{"question":"306000090000009060080346020103458679457600000608270000001004902860015040900000500","answer":"316527894245189367789346125123458679457691238698273451531764982862915743974832516"},"234":{"question":"001908657006100409080050100000009768405780000807200010010000000070002005000005241","answer":"241938657356127489789456123123549768465781392897263514512394876674812935938675241"},"235":{"question":"000003052005140000009050000120065080056008203890002065341007806500900307078000001","answer":"614873952235149678789256134123465789456798213897312465341527896562981347978634521"},"236":{"question":"284009060100040009070000240312400098450090020700002450500080970067004000943700010","answer":"284579163135246789679138245312457698456891327798362451521683974867914532943725816"},"237":{"question":"000008000100007509608000234000000800000801302097000140042716050780002460060580720","answer":"529348617134267589678159234213475896456891372897623145342716958785932461961584723"},"238":{"question":"900000000104000000008000100213000006050091037780063001001005072602034010805700304","answer":"927158643164329785538476129213547896456891237789263451341685972672934518895712364"},"239":{"question":"000060000000007080009000100215300090347891526060070304400785060590614807000900050","answer":"783169245154237689629458173215346798347891526968572314431785962592614837876923451"},"240":{"question":"000605032000000009000000040210050008006097004090000356401762005670981400002503071","answer":"149675832327814569568239147213456798856397214794128356431762985675981423982543671"},"241":{"question":"908005010103008500400020078200300807005090004709204005530040006000000750007503200","answer":"978635412123478569456129378214356897365897124789214635531742986642981753897563241"},"242":{"question":"000084000000000000070009300014630700056700014789040000030806007641900035097453001","answer":"123584976965327148478169352214635789356798214789241563532816497641972835897453621"},"243":{"question":"609000000020400080000030000200006790300801420005070000001080900006013852982745613","answer":"649528137123467589758139246214356798367891425895274361531682974476913852982745613"},"244":{"question":"000000006020609000000400020204500780006097200000000000431200097762003040985714600","answer":"149325876528679413673481925294536781316897254857142369431268597762953148985714632"},"245":{"question":"000170000103000670000068005204085700300091000090020350500846900086012003002507816","answer":"658173294123459678479268135214385769365791482897624351531846927786912543942537816"},"246":{"question":"000700040023400000000180000200300897306090004008010306000542008842901000900600412","answer":"189723645523469781467185239214356897356897124798214356631542978842971563975638412"},"247":{"question":"005000207000050009780230105004305098306000400800000006408072000502940000000003524","answer":"615894237243157689789236145124365798396718452857429316438572961562941873971683524"},"248":{"question":"605000108100500000009107006004006000006000204008204500507000680840000930960035740","answer":"625349178173568429489127356214756893756983214398214567537491682841672935962835741"},"249":{"question":"940800100000009600000005240210400000406000000789312065301074900004983701800001530","answer":"942867153135249678678135249213456897456798312789312465321574986564983721897621534"},"250":{"question":"706000200003000089009100340004305090300000060600714520030002608800640900065871032","answer":"746938215123456789589127346214365897357289164698714523431592678872643951965871432"},"251":{"question":"250060890340080000000030000100000709465090000090002400502043978630070020908020034","answer":"251764893346189257789235146123456789465897312897312465512643978634978521978521634"},"252":{"question":"010000006030007000000040000100056008000091000869023000341078952580004607706500041","answer":"214389576935267184678145329123456798457891263869723415341678952582914637796532841"},"253":{"question":"300200005020000000680400003010006080400008231000023040502614970007005000960872350","answer":"374261895125389467689457123213546789456798231798123546532614978847935612961872354"},"254":{"question":"000040000020009460000000000000000780306008004097402356000070092648901503972835601","answer":"165247938723189465489356127214563789356798214897412356531674892648921573972835641"},"255":{"question":"030007500000069478000008103000006709000800361800070045302600010761025804080000002","answer":"438217596125369478679458123213546789547892361896173245352684917761925834984731652"},"256":{"question":"007000000000000000080207100103405090400080207000610354301506002005001043902830001","answer":"217359486534168729689247135123475698456983217798612354341596872865721943972834561"},"257":{"question":"008501006023007080006000000010605000060098214000042035031800060002953871000016003","answer":"798521346123467589456389127214635798365798214879142635531874962642953871987216453"},"258":{"question":"900000000003007509000009024010030790356098201780000356031085007500900802092600005","answer":"925864173643127589178359624214536798356798241789412356431285967567941832892673415"},"259":{"question":"000032547030000080000000003003506000006798200009213400302000970000000312905301060","answer":"691832547234157689857469123123546798546798231789213456312684975468975312975321864"},"260":{"question":"042000000000000000000346120000050609050001000097603014324018950560032740071000000","answer":"642175398135289467789346125213457689456891273897623514324718956568932741971564832"},"261":{"question":"500000070030007600700100005000005000457800006608020050301580007806000513975030842","answer":"562348179139257684784196235213465798457819326698723451321584967846972513975631842"},"262":{"question":"000000304000020500709305026100056098060000003007203000502804000600901000070032641","answer":"251689374346127589789345126123456798465798213897213465512864937634971852978532641"},"263":{"question":"980200000030167500060409000103500090050700001090000640310050006645970002000021354","answer":"981235467234167589567489123123546798456798231798312645312854976645973812879621354"},"264":{"question":"000009000230008000009406103103040096450892000090300005300020080570000630908013700","answer":"614239578235178469789456123123547896456892317897361245361725984572984631948613752"},"265":{"question":"007000460120050789409000005000065800305009040698000000501000008700801500002500614","answer":"857912463123456789469738125214365897375189246698247351531624978746891532982573614"},"266":{"question":"810794002204000000000030000100065097057819203008020010000070908000980320900543670","answer":"816794532234156789579238146123465897457819263698327415341672958765981324982543671"},"267":{"question":"000705001000060009578100000010456008000891203609200000000010980045903002060082437","answer":"396725841124368579578149326213456798457891263689237154732614985845973612961582437"},"268":{"question":"000000000005037600700040105000059000407080090608070500530060907870910006964703001","answer":"316598472245137689789246135123459768457681293698372514531864927872915346964723851"},"269":{"question":"607090050004300600500007030010005000050010027790600140300580000802040513965700002","answer":"637294851124358679589167234213475968456819327798623145341582796872946513965731482"},"270":{"question":"040020097100079450670400000000006000300800000000100065431285970700903840080060501","answer":"548321697123679458679458123214536789356897214897142365431285976765913842982764531"},"271":{"question":"054102000100670400609008020000000709306000005798000300432061097507023040060704002","answer":"854132976123679458679458123215346789346897215798215364432561897587923641961784532"},"272":{"question":"002035060056008249089000100100400690040089310000010504030500786004020953070000020","answer":"412935867356178249789246135123457698547689312698312574231594786864721953975863421"},"273":{"question":"001000020000100000589040136100000897457800000006703415000600950000981302008530601","answer":"641358729273196584589247136132465897457819263896723415314672958765981342928534671"},"274":{"question":"040000530000000000080357120100475800000200300890003245000000002000034901968721453","answer":"741962538235148679689357124123475896456289317897613245314596782572834961968721453"},"275":{"question":"002703006100200570000000120013000709060897000090030005021600000580924300947381000","answer":"452713896138269574679458123813542769265897431794136285321675948586924317947381652"},"276":{"question":"831000046005100780670008000020000600450009000708300051307080902560090004080020570","answer":"831957246245136789679248135123475698456819327798362451317584962562793814984621573"},"277":{"question":"360000000105000680709020300010008090056009008007610052500700064670500901040801500","answer":"364985217125347689789126345213458796456279138897613452531792864678534921942861573"},"278":{"question":"000000000000408079450230000014306007300090045079824016031002050092040080005073900","answer":"968517432123468579457239168214356897386791245579824316631982754792145683845673921"},"279":{"question":"000032005000006089060470100023007608056089310790360250002090800000000900907620030","answer":"871932465234156789569478123123547698456289317798361254312795846645813972987624531"},"280":{"question":"009740830000000070070100050214000700000897020007200060532080007740005680980003510","answer":"159742836423568179678139254214356798365897421897214365532681947741925683986473512"},"281":{"question":"060040297020500000000260130200050089300091020608020051030600902042000016006000043","answer":"563148297721539468489267135214756389357891624698423751135684972942375816876912543"},"282":{"question":"000200500100000000400000000010300806365000472809620003501742960040008010080510020","answer":"693287541128459637457136289214375896365891472879624153531742968742968315986513724"},"283":{"question":"200000500145000009680300000010070090450080237008600000021704600073010942900802700","answer":"237149568145268379689357124312475896456981237798623415521794683873516942964832751"},"284":{"question":"000800000120050709508300000010037098050198047000064010431680000002900835900000461","answer":"679812354123456789548379126214537698356198247897264513431685972762941835985723461"},"285":{"question":"004079200025006700670020300200007090406892000000013052001000976000961003000735010","answer":"184379265325146789679528341213457698456892137798613452531284976847961523962735814"},"286":{"question":"007000001000067080060100000200050798450791306796200005001872050800000600000034812","answer":"387529461124367589569148237213456798458791326796283145631872954842915673975634812"},"287":{"question":"508160000100007689007080005200005896006090007000004300000000000872906513000008762","answer":"538169274124357689967482135241735896356891427789624351615273948872946513493518762"},"288":{"question":"060008000000009408080000200013457009046800000897060010000700906658003741000010020","answer":"362548197175239468984176253213457689546891372897362514421785936658923741739614825"},"289":{"question":"000032000023400000000180005010360798005208416698010050000826000002901000006003800","answer":"157632984823459167469187235214365798375298416698714352731826549582941673946573821"},"290":{"question":"000900200000000000409000050204350000065700104890240060538670940600800702072013685","answer":"153964278726538419489127356214356897365789124897241563538672941641895732972413685"},"291":{"question":"000030000030000580500400100020540790406708231790000045010054976600000812070601000","answer":"167835429234169587589427163321546798456798231798312645813254976645973812972681354"},"292":{"question":"000300005004050600060000030000075096050090300080623051300010960671984000890506700","answer":"127369845934158672568247139413875296256491387789623451345712968671984523892536714"},"293":{"question":"000703040000000009000000000000000807400070302700010060025684971841000653900530428","answer":"158793246234156789679248135513462897496875312782319564325684971841927653967531428"},"294":{"question":"000000307130060000600308005203406000006089013090123006300802004000035600057604830","answer":"482591367135267489679348125213456798546789213798123546361872954824935671957614832"},"295":{"question":"001304000004000000000058034003085090400090003098603410312806009045000026967002000","answer":"581324967734169258629758134173485692456291783298673415312846579845917326967532841"},"296":{"question":"001093000000000080060248007000456000056000312090000460318600074042070800075030601","answer":"281793546734561289569248137123456798456987312897312465318625974642179853975834621"},"297":{"question":"500000001000250000000100200003460780400090020000723004321504067046907000900602040","answer":"562378491134259678789146235213465789457891326698723154321584967846937512975612843"},"298":{"question":"000100000003060000468070000200056000370091006000407350000082064602905000987004012","answer":"729143685153268479468579123214356798375891246896427351531782964642915837987634512"},"299":{"question":"070040000000070000450009070010350800060097214790000300531004980047001000002560041","answer":"873145629129678453456239178214356897365897214798412365531724986647981532982563741"}};


const miniBox1 = document.getElementById('mini-box-1');
miniBox1.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 0) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox2 = document.getElementById('mini-box-2');
miniBox2.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 1) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox3 = document.getElementById('mini-box-3');
miniBox3.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 2) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox4 = document.getElementById('mini-box-4');
miniBox4.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 3) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox5 = document.getElementById('mini-box-5');
miniBox5.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 4) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox6 = document.getElementById('mini-box-6');
miniBox6.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 5) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox7 = document.getElementById('mini-box-7');
miniBox7.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 6) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox8 = document.getElementById('mini-box-8');
miniBox8.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 7) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox9 = document.getElementById('mini-box-9');
miniBox9.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 8) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });

const allBoxes = [miniBox1, miniBox2, miniBox3, miniBox4, miniBox5, miniBox6, miniBox7, miniBox8, miniBox9];
const allLines = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('line'));

const minimizeVars = ['box1DecreaseSize', 'box2DecreaseSize', 'box3DecreaseSize', 'box4DecreaseSize', 'box5DecreaseSize', 'box6DecreaseSize', 'box7DecreaseSize', 'box8DecreaseSize', 'box9DecreaseSize'];
const maximizeVars = ['box1IncreaseSize', 'box2IncreaseSize', 'box3IncreaseSize', 'box4IncreaseSize', 'box5IncreaseSize', 'box6IncreaseSize', 'box7IncreaseSize', 'box8IncreaseSize', 'box9IncreaseSize'];
let isMaximizedBool = false;

// number of the box thats maximized
let miniBoxOnNumber;

// all maximizable boxes
const allTapBoxes = getReadingOrientationNumbers();

// the game number (0-299)
let GAME_NUMBER = 0;

// the game state
let GAME_STATE = easyGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the original state of board without touching it
let GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = easyGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the menu button orientation boolean
let isMenuOpen = false;

// gets all 81 boxes in box order and returns them in reading left to right order
function getReadingOrientationNumbers() {
    let temp = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('tap-box'));
    let ret = [];

    let one = 0;
    let two = 9;
    let three = 18;
    for (let i = 0; i < 3; i++) {
        for (let j = 0; j < 3; j++) {
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(one, one + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(two, two + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(three, three + 3));
            one = one + 3;
            two = two + 3;
            three = three + 3;
        }
        one = one + 18;
        two = two + 18;
        three = three + 18;
    }
    return ret;
}

// Maximizes first box, and hides rest. 
function miniBoxMaximize(num) {
    allBoxes[num].style.animation = `${maximizeVars[num]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
    miniBoxOnNumber = num;
    isMaximizedBool = true;
    hideRest(allBoxes[num]);
    console.log('maximize');
}

// if there is a box enlarged, it will minimize it
function minimizeMiniBox() {
    if (isMaximizedBool) {
        allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber].style.animation = `${minimizeVars[miniBoxOnNumber]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
        unHideRest(allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber]);
        isMaximizedBool = false;
        console.log('minimize');
    }
}

// Given a box, hides rest except given box
function hideRest(miniBox) {
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// Given a box, shows rest except given box since given box has its own animation going on
async function unHideRest(miniBox) {
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// this is for the individual 81 numbers!!
async function clickedTapBox(boxNumber) {
    let question = easyGames[0]['question'];
    if (isMaximizedBool && question[boxNumber] === '0') {  // This ensures that the tap-box number isnt increased by 1 unless the box is maximized
        let theNumber = allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML;
        if (theNumber === '') {
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = 1;
            //GAME_STATE[boxNumber] = '1';
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, '1');
            console.log(GAME_STATE);
            localStorage.setItem('easyGameState', GAME_STATE);
        } else {
            theNumber = parseInt(theNumber);
            if (theNumber === 9) {
                theNumber = '';
            } else {
                theNumber = theNumber + 1;
            }
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.1s ease-out forwards';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 100));
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = theNumber;
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
            // save game state
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, theNumber.toString());
            console.log(GAME_STATE);
            localStorage.setItem('easyGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
    if (isSolved()) {
        console.log('game solved!!!');
    }
}

function isSolved() {
    if (GAME_STATE === easyGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer']) {
        return true;
    } else {
        return false;
    }
}

// personal replace function
String.prototype.replaceAt = function(index, replacement) {
    return this.substr(0, index) + replacement + this.substr(index + replacement.length);
}

// this will start the game either from where left off or new game
function fillStartingState() {
    for (let i = 0; i < allTapBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i];
            allTapBoxes[i].style.color = '#545454';
        } else if (GAME_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_STATE[i];
        }
    }
}
// this needs to happen before the function call below
if (!localStorage.getItem("easyGameNumber")) {
    localStorage.setItem("easyGameNumber", "0");
    localStorage.setItem('easyGameState', easyGames[0]['question']);
} else {
    GAME_NUMBER = localStorage.getItem('easyGameNumber');
    GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = easyGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    GAME_STATE = localStorage.getItem('easyGameState');
}
fillStartingState();

async function quickSolve() {
    let one = 0;
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0' && one === 0) {
            one = 1;
        } else if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0') {
            let theNumber = easyGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer'][i];
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = theNumber;
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(i, theNumber.toString());
            localStorage.setItem('easyGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
}

async function menuButtonClicked() {
    if (!isMenuOpen) {
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToMenuDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuOpen 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'hidden';
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim1 3s infinite ease-in-out';  
        isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
    } else {
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToGameDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuClose 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
        document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'visible';
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim 3s infinite ease-in-out'; 
        isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
    }
}
function skipClicked() {
    console.log('skipppp');
}
function clearInputClicked() {
    console.log('clearInputttt');
}
function hintClicked() {
    console.log('hint clicked');
}